https://bellracing.com/privacy-policy-cookie-restriction-mode

Forced Air
Head & Neck (HANS)
Privacy Statement
Bell Racing USA LLC respects your right to privacy and it is a matter of great importance. We are committed to implementing the procedures and technology necessary to safeguard your information.
Bell Racing USA LLC collects personal information necessary for completing a purchase transaction including your name, address, telephone number, e-mail address and payment information. Bell Racing USA LLC also provides the opportunity for customers to opt-in to receive additional e-mails with information regarding Bell Racing products. Any information collected on the Bell Racing USA site will be kept strictly confidential and will not be sold or disclosed to other parties.
Please contact us at 800-237-2700 or e-mail info@bellracing.com if you have any questions or need additional information.
Privacy Policy
Personal Information
When you interact with us, we automatically receive and store certain types of information, such as the content you view, the date and time that you view this content, the products you purchase, or your location information associated with your IP address. We use the information we collect to serve you more relevant advertisements (referred to as "Retargeting"). This is statistical information used to monitor the usage of our website and for advertising purposes. This information does not include personal information.
Photos & Submitted Information
When you post, or submit any content (including photos, videos or text) to Bell Racing USA to share publicly through the news section of the website, social media or other means, you acknowledge that you are the owner of this material, are submitting with express consent of the owner of the material and that you are 18 years of age or older.
By submitting material, you are granting Bell Racing and anyone authorized by Bell Racing a royalty free, perpetual, irrevocable, non-exclusive, unrestricted, worldwide license to use, copy, modify, transmit, sell, exploit, create derivative works from, distribute, and/or publicly perform or display such material, in whole or in part, in any manner or medium, now known or hereafter developed, for any purpose. By submitting information to Bell Racing you warrant and represent the use of the content will not violate or infringe upon the trademark, tradename, copyright, artistic, and/or other rights of any third-party and the consent of no other person or entity is required.
Bell Racing reserves the right to reject or remove any submitted materials that are not in compliance with the above policy. If you are a copyright owner and believe someone has submitted material to Bell Racing that constitutes a copyright infringement, please e-mail info@bellracing.com.
Cookies
As you browse bellracing.com, advertising cookies will be placed on your computer so that we can understand what you are interested in. Our display advertising partner, AdRoll, then enables us to present you with retargeting advertising on other sites based on your previous interaction with bellracing.com. The techniques our partners employ do not collect personal information such as your name, email address, postal address or telephone number. You can visit this page to opt out of AdRoll and their partners' targeted advertising.
Security
We implement a secure processing server on our site when collecting information to ensure a high level of security for your personal information entered such as bank details and credit card information.
Get a Quote for
Customer Name
Customer Email
Phone Number
Comment
Submit
Would you like to save this store view for the next visit?
YES
NO
